(function(){
  var data = touchtile.data;
  data.glyphs = [
    {"question": "1", "answer": "1"},
    {"question": "3", "answer": "3"},
    {"question": "Abandon", "answer": "Abandon"},
    {"question": "Adapt", "answer": "Adapt"},
    {"question": "Advance", "answer": "Advance"},
    {"question": "After", "answer": "After"},
    {"question": "Again", "answer": "Again"},
    {"question": "All", "answer": "All"},
    {"question": "Answer", "answer": "Answer"},
    {"question": "Attack", "answer": "Attack"},
    {"question": "Avoid", "answer": "Avoid"},
    {"question": "Barrier", "answer": "Barrier"},
    {"question": "Before", "answer": "Before"},
    {"question": "Begin", "answer": "Begin"},
    {"question": "Body", "answer": "Body"},
    {"question": "Breathe", "answer": "Breathe"},
    {"question": "Capture", "answer": "Capture"},
    {"question": "Change", "answer": "Change"},
    {"question": "Chaos", "answer": "Chaos"},
    {"question": "Civilization", "answer": "Civilization"},
    {"question": "Clear", "answer": "Clear"},
    {"question": "ClearAll", "answer": "ClearAll"},
    {"question": "Complex", "answer": "Complex"},
    {"question": "Conflict", "answer": "Conflict"},
    {"question": "Consequence", "answer": "Consequence"},
    {"question": "Contemplate", "answer": "Contemplate"},
    {"question": "Courage", "answer": "Courage"},
    {"question": "Create", "answer": "Create"},
    {"question": "Danger", "answer": "Danger"},
    {"question": "Data", "answer": "Data"},
    {"question": "Defend", "answer": "Defend"},
    {"question": "Destination", "answer": "Destination"},
    {"question": "Destiny", "answer": "Destiny"},
    {"question": "Destroy", "answer": "Destroy"},
    {"question": "Deteriorate", "answer": "Deteriorate"},
    {"question": "Die", "answer": "Die"},
    {"question": "Difficult", "answer": "Difficult"},
    {"question": "Discover", "answer": "Discover"},
    {"question": "Distance", "answer": "Distance"},
    {"question": "Easy", "answer": "Easy"},
    {"question": "End", "answer": "End"},
    {"question": "Enlightened", "answer": "Enlightened"},
    {"question": "Equal", "answer": "Equal"},
    {"question": "Escape", "answer": "Escape"},
    {"question": "Evolution", "answer": "Evolution"},
    {"question": "Failure", "answer": "Failure"},
    {"question": "Fear", "answer": "Fear"},
    {"question": "Field", "answer": "Field"},
    {"question": "Follow", "answer": "Follow"},
    {"question": "Forget", "answer": "Forget"},
    {"question": "Future", "answer": "Future"},
    {"question": "Gain", "answer": "Gain"},
    {"question": "Grow", "answer": "Grow"},
    {"question": "Harm", "answer": "Harm"},
    {"question": "Harmony", "answer": "Harmony"},
    {"question": "Have", "answer": "Have"},
    {"question": "Help", "answer": "Help"},
    {"question": "Hide", "answer": "Hide"},
    {"question": "Human", "answer": "Human"},
    {"question": "I", "answer": "I"},
    {"question": "Idea", "answer": "Idea"},
    {"question": "Ignore", "answer": "Ignore"},
    {"question": "Imperfect", "answer": "Imperfect"},
    {"question": "Improve", "answer": "Improve"},
    {"question": "Impure", "answer": "Impure"},
    {"question": "Intelligence", "answer": "Intelligence"},
    {"question": "Interrupt", "answer": "Interrupt"},
    {"question": "Journey", "answer": "Journey"},
    {"question": "Key", "answer": "Key"},
    {"question": "Knowledge", "answer": "Knowledge"},
    {"question": "L", "answer": "L"},
    {"question": "Lead", "answer": "Lead"},
    {"question": "Legacy", "answer": "Legacy"},
    {"question": "Less", "answer": "Less"},
    {"question": "Liberate", "answer": "Liberate"},
    {"question": "Lie", "answer": "Lie"},
    {"question": "Link", "answer": "Link"},
    {"question": "Live Again", "answer": "Live Again"},
    {"question": "Again", "answer": "Again"},
    {"question": "Lose", "answer": "Lose"},
    {"question": "Message", "answer": "Message"},
    {"question": "Mind", "answer": "Mind"},
    {"question": "More", "answer": "More"},
    {"question": "Mystery", "answer": "Mystery"},
    {"question": "N'zeer", "answer": "N'zeer"},
    {"question": "N", "answer": "N"},
    {"question": "Nature", "answer": "Nature"},
    {"question": "Nemesis", "answer": "Nemesis"},
    {"question": "New", "answer": "New"},
    {"question": "Not", "answer": "Not"},
    {"question": "Nourish", "answer": "Nourish"},
    {"question": "Old", "answer": "Old"},
    {"question": "Open", "answer": "Open"},
    {"question": "Openall", "answer": "Openall"},
    {"question": "Osiris", "answer": "Osiris"},
    {"question": "Past", "answer": "Past"},
    {"question": "Path", "answer": "Path"},
    {"question": "Perfection", "answer": "Perfection"},
    {"question": "Perspective", "answer": "Perspective"},
    {"question": "Portal", "answer": "Portal"},
    {"question": "Potential", "answer": "Potential"},
    {"question": "Presence", "answer": "Presence"},
    {"question": "Present", "answer": "Present"},
    {"question": "Pure", "answer": "Pure"},
    {"question": "Pursue", "answer": "Pursue"},
    {"question": "Question", "answer": "Question"},
    {"question": "React", "answer": "React"},
    {"question": "Rebel", "answer": "Rebel"},
    {"question": "Recharge", "answer": "Recharge"},
    {"question": "Reduce", "answer": "Reduce"},
    {"question": "Resistance", "answer": "Resistance"},
    {"question": "Restraint", "answer": "Restraint"},
    {"question": "Retreat", "answer": "Retreat"},
    {"question": "Safety", "answer": "Safety"},
    {"question": "Save", "answer": "Save"},
    {"question": "Search", "answer": "Search"},
    {"question": "See", "answer": "See"},
    {"question": "Self", "answer": "Self"},
    {"question": "Separate", "answer": "Separate"},
    {"question": "Shapers", "answer": "Shapers"},
    {"question": "Share", "answer": "Share"},
    {"question": "Shield", "answer": "Shield"},
    {"question": "Simple", "answer": "Simple"},
    {"question": "Soul", "answer": "Soul"},
    {"question": "Stability", "answer": "Stability"},
    {"question": "Star", "answer": "Star"},
    {"question": "Strong", "answer": "Strong"},
    {"question": "Sustain", "answer": "Sustain"},
    {"question": "Technology", "answer": "Technology"},
    {"question": "Them", "answer": "Them"},
    {"question": "Toast", "answer": "Toast"},
    {"question": "Together", "answer": "Together"},
    {"question": "Truth", "answer": "Truth"},
    {"question": "Unbounded", "answer": "Unbounded"},
    {"question": "Use", "answer": "Use"},
    {"question": "Victory", "answer": "Victory"},
    {"question": "Want", "answer": "Want"},
    {"question": "We", "answer": "We"},
    {"question": "Weak", "answer": "Weak"},
    {"question": "Worth", "answer": "Worth"},
    {"question": "XM", "answer": "XM"},
    {"question": "You", "answer": "You"}
  ];
})();
